嗨  宝贝儿
Hey, babe.
见到你真好
Nice to see you, too.
亲爱的
Honey?
没事吧
Are you okay?
你们真是疾控中心的吗
You expect me to believe you're cdc?
什么
Excuse me?
没什么  只是你们早来了一天
It's just that you're a day early.
史上第一次
First time in history i haven't sat on my ass
我不用干等
Waiting for you people.
新管理班子
New administration.
值得你的信任
A change you can believe in.
好吧
Right.
米特·塞维尔
Meet xavier.
生于1984年4月3日
Date of birth -- april 3, 1984.
我知道
I know.
我做了两次DNA测试
I ran the dna twice.
肯定就是他本人
That's definitely him.
看来他不怎么涂防晒霜
Well, he wasn't big on the sunscreen, huh?
你有何想法
So, what's your theory?
我只可确定  死者为男性  25岁
All I know is, decedent's male, 25 years old,
因衰老而死
And he died of old age.
你说得没错  肯定有灵异
You were right about this one. it's definitely a job.
我就知道
Thought so.
镇上还有其他受害者吗
Any other stiffs in town?
只有一名死者
Just the one body.
还有呢
Anything else?
有些人失踪  但这种大小的镇 也很正常
Couple missing persons, but usual for a town this size.
好吧  去查清楚
Well, check 'em out.
你认为这其中有关联吗
You think they're connected?
-预感有  - 明白了
- Call it a hunch. - You got it.
顺便  你最近如何
And, by the way, how you doing?
什么如何
Doing?
是啊
Yeah.
你也知道  总体而言
You know, just...in general?
你是说我的腿吗
Oh, you mean my legs.
我抱着哈根达斯泪流满面呢
Well, i'm just weepin' in my haagen-dazs.
呆子
Idjit.
这是最近照的
That's the most recent.
他失踪多久了
How long has he been missing?
他星期二晚上没有回家
Oh, I knew right away
我就知道不对劲
When he didn't come home tuesday night.
他下班后常去什么地方吗
Is there someplace he likes to go after work, maybe?
比如酒吧之类
A favorite bar?
不
No.
一般在星期二  他总是工作得晚些
Tuesdays, he always works a bit late,
但他总是直接回家
But he always comes straight home.
我能四处看看吗  女士
May i use your facilities, ma'am?
"工作到很晚"吗  鬼才信
"working late," my ass.
至少他很专一
Well, at least he's consistent.
每周二都定同一间钟点房
Same room every tuesday, hourly rates.
真希望我到了那把年纪还能欲望充沛
Hope I got that kind of kick when I'm his age.
我们活得了那么久吗
Yeah, like either of us will live that long.
也对
True.
好吧  猜那里面有什么呢
So... what do you think's in there?
皱巴巴黏糊糊的尸体吗
A wrinkly, gooey corpse.
噢  天啊
Oh, god! oh, god!
天啊
Oh! oh, god!
搞毛啊
What the...
老天
Oh. god.
果然又软又黏
It's gooey.
抱歉
Sorry. uh...
进错房间
Got the wrong room.
快关门
Close the door!
纹身不错啊
Nice tattoo.
有认识叫克里夫·维洛的吗
Happen to know anybody named Cliff Whitlow?
从没听过
Never heard of him.
那就怪了
Well, that's weird.
你带着他的钱包呢
'cause you're carrying his wallet.
你妻子告诉我们你这里有胎记
Your wife told us about your, uh, birthmark there.
不错
That's nice.
你看起来很好嘛  克里夫
Well, you look great, cliff.
你是不是整容了还是怎样
Did you get some work done?
能让我们单独谈谈吗
Could you give us some privacy?
谢谢
Thanks.
回见
Bye.
千万不能告诉我老婆
Please don't tell my wife
别急
Slow down.
求你们  要是被她知道  我就死定了
I'm begging you. as far as she knows, i'm dead.
看在上帝的份上  替我保密
For the love of god, let's keep it that way.
你怎可能是克里夫·维洛
How can you possibly be cliff whitlow?
我不能说
I can't tell you.
不然我们告诉你老婆去
Well, either you tell us or we tell the missus.
好吧
Okay! okay!
是一场游戏
It was a game.
电子游戏那种的
Like...xbox?
啥电子游戏
What's xbox?
不  是扑克游戏  高风险的
No. poker -- high-stakes.
不赌现金  而是生命
Instead of cash, you play for years.
那是什么意思
What is that supposed to mean?
我知道这听起来很疯狂
Look, I know it sounds crazy.
在酒吧里遇到一个男人  他邀我玩的
Guy comes up to me at a bar, invites me to play.
他给了我25个怪异的筹码
Gives me 25 of these weirdo poker chips, right?
对着他们念了堆听不懂的咒语
Chants some mumbo humbo over them,
声称它们现在代表25年
Says now they're 25 years.
我还嘲笑他
I'm laughing...
但我出来后
But then I come out up.
就变成这样了
And look at me.
-什么咒语  - 我咋知道
- What was he chanting? - How should i know?
我只知道  我屁股也不疼了
All I know is, my bad hip's good,
眼镜也摔了
I threw away my glasses.
这儿还有成堆的妞儿等着我
One of those ladies was here for free!
这男人真是奇迹创造者
Man's some kind of miracle worker.
那个奇迹创造者长啥样呢
What does this miracle worker look like?
一个男人
Just a guy.
35岁左右  棕色头发
Maybe 35, brown hair.
爱尔兰口音  他叫帕特里克
Irish accent. his name was patrick.
好吧  这游戏是在哪玩的
All right, all right. where's this game at?
他说他喜欢旅行
He said he likes to keep moving.
从不固定待在一个地方
never stays in one bar
只能由他来选择你
And he finds you.
谢了  克里夫
Thank you, cliff.
还有
Oh, and, uh...
这风格不错  保持保持
Stay classy.
这听起来太疯狂了吧
It sounds crazy, right?
不  事实上的确有这样的传说
No. there's lore on it.
几世纪前
Goes back centuries.
小镇上会出现卡牌旅人
Traveling card player pops into town.
如果你打败他  就能赢会黄金时光
You beat him, you get your best years back.
当然  大多数人都输了
'course, most folks lose.
那就能解释皱巴巴的尸体了
Well, that would explain the crunchy corpse.
据说  那家伙玩的一手玩牌
Supposedly, this player's a hell of a card shark.
赢了很多年华
Got a lot of years in the bank.
你找到他出没的酒吧了吗
You find the bar he's working in yet?
这镇上酒吧太多了
There's a lot of dives in this town.
我们准备分头找
We're gonna have to split up.
那你还讲什么电话
Well, why you still talking to me?
查到了吗
Find anything?
屁都没有  你呢
Yeah, a whole bunch of squat. you?
-还没有  - 好吧
- No, not a thing.  - All right.
要是没找什么的话  2点回旅馆去
Well, you come up dry, circle back to the motel in two.
轮到你买晚饭了
Your turn to grab dinner.
-和平时吃的一样吗  - 加培根
- Usually.  - Extra bacon.
来杯啤酒吗
Can I get a beer?
好
Yep.
你知不知道
You wouldn't happen to know of a poker game
这里面有人在玩扑克
Going on in back, would you?
这是酒吧  不是赌场
It's a bar, not a casino.
有个叫本的朋友说你知道
My friend ben told me you'd know.
不认识什么叫本的
Don't know any ben.
当然啦
Sure you do.
自作聪明的秃头  一个花花肠子
You know, balding, smart-ass, real ladies' man?
听着  朋友  告诉你
Listen, pal, I told you --
我根本不认识本
I don't know any ben.
也不知道什么扑克游戏
I don't know nothing about a game.
你确定吗  因为
You sure? 'cause, uh...
你好像真的认识你哦
He sure seems to know you.
绕到后面  乘电梯下去
'round back. take the elevator down.
鲍比
Bobby?
你在这儿干嘛
What the hell are you doing here?
我来种花的  你以为啊
Planting daisies. what's it look like?
我来查案子
Came in on the case.
你先下手为强了
And you beat me here?
很明显  大脑战胜大腿
Well, brains trumps legs, apparently.
你找到玩扑克的人了
So, you found the game?
没错
Yep.
你阻止他们了吗
Did you stop it?
鲍比
Bobby?
不能算阻止
Not exactly.
你做了什么
What did you do?
我玩了游戏  行了吧
I played, okay?
结果呢
And?
我输了
I lost.
你在说笑吗
Are you kidding me?
你和男巫玩牌
You played some -- some he-witch?
别用这种口气教训我
Don't you take that tone with me.
你这笨蛋
You idiot!
这是我自己的年华  随我怎么用
They're my years! I can do what i want!
你输了多少
How many did you lose?
25年
25.
这事儿还没完
We're not done.
你说你会读心术吗
So, you're saying that you're a mind reader.
得啦  没有的事
Ah, come on. no such thing.
但我能分析人的心理
But i can read people.
好比你这位美丽的女伴吧
Take your lovely companion here.
从她精致的姿势判断
I'd say, judging from her exquisite posture,
她以前是位舞者
She used to be a dancer.
不怎么喝酒
Not much of a drinker.
很有主见
Very independent.
喜欢冒险
Looking for adventure.
嘿  伙计
Hey, man.
不好意思
Excuse me.
能和你谈谈吗
Can I borrow you for a sec?
好吧  当然啦  太好了
Oh, yeah. of course. great.
见到你真好
Good to see you.
失陪一下  两位
Would you two please excuse me?
真抱歉
Sorry to cut you short
打断你和目标夫妇之间的谈话
With mr. and mrs. easy marks over there.
没什么
Oh, no big.
也不完全失败
Wasn't a total loss.
听着  你或许觉得
Look, I don't know what it is you think i did
我对你的妻子或女友
To your wife or girlfriend,
母亲或姐姐做了什么
Mother or sister,
但是要知道  我的感受是真实的
But, uh, i just want you to know, my feelings were real.
那不关我的事  你这男巫
That ain't my problem, man-witch.
你欠我朋友一些年华
You owe my friend some years.
哦  原来如此
Oh, that's what this is.
不好意思  但他输了
I'm sorry. he lost.
生命一下子就停止
Them's the breaks.
那就放了他
Well, then un-lose him.
来吧  开枪好了
Oh, go ahead and shoot me,
如果这能使你好受点
If it makes you feel better.
此外  我是想
Besides, i could use a good...
挠挠痒
You know...tickle.
你想要回年华吗  好吧
You want years? great.
那就和我玩牌吧
Play me for 'em.
好
Fine.
迪恩  不要
Dean, no!
那是我自己的年华  随我怎么用
They're my years. I can do what i want.
要含片吗
Lozenge?
啥  这东西不可疑
What? it's barely linty.
那随便你了  我只是为你好
Okay, well, suit yourself. just trying to help.
行了  快开始吧
All right, all right. come on. let's do this.
你清楚其中的条件吧
You understand the terms?
下注25年
Buy-in's 25 years.
我要赌50年
Make it 50.
我喜欢你这种爽快人
I like the cut of your jib.
25.
25年
That's 25 years.
给他了
They go to him.
他现在要兑现
And he's cashing out.
-迪恩  - 鲍比
- Dean! - Bobby.
你确定
You sure?
确定
Yes.
你刚刚可浪费了25年
That's 25 years you just pissed away.
最好有把握能赢回来
Better be sure you can win them back.
发牌吧
Shuffle up and deal.
这会很有意思的
This is gonna be fun.
迪恩
Hey, Dean?
有发现吗
You find anything?
可以这么说
Uh, you might say.
你他娘是谁
Who the hell are you?!
哥们  冷静
Dude, relax.
是我
It's me.
迪恩
Dean?
发生什么事了
What the hell happened?
我  你知道  找到那赌局了
I, you know... found the game.
你
You found...
我记得你说你牌打得好啊
I thought you said you were g-good at poker.
我打得确实好  闭嘴
I am. Shut up.
怎么  想冲老年人开枪吗
So, you were just gonna shoot some old guy? Is that...
我不知道你之前怎样  但是  你照过镜子吗
I didn't know what you were. I mean, h-have you seen you?
你看起来就像
You look like...
《泰坦尼克号》里的老女人  我知道  闭嘴
The old chick in "Titanic." I know. Shut up.
我想说的是皇帝帕尔帕庭[《星球大战》]
I was gonna say "Emperor Palpatine".
看来你见过约翰·麦凯恩了
I see you met John McCain there.
好  你们俩谁能告诉我到底怎么回事
Yeah. Either of you want to tell me what happened?
鲍比犯傻了  就是这么回事
Bobby's an idiot. That's what happened.
没人让你去赌
Hey, nobody asked you to play.
对  我本该眼睁睁看你死的
Right. I should have just let you die.
还有  没人让你输
And for damn sure, nobody asked you to lose!
简直就像《斗气老顽童》
It's like "Grumpy Old Men."
-闭嘴  萨姆  - 闭嘴  萨姆
- Shut up, Sam! - Shut up, Sam!
你到底怎么想的
What the hell were you thinking?
他是巫师
He's a witch.
从有人传紧身衣起就开始玩扑克了
He's been playing poker since guys wore tights.
你就是不懂
You just don't get...
不  我懂  鲍比
Yeah, I get it, Bobby.
你看到了让时光逆转
You saw a chance to turn the hands of the clock back
离开那该死的轮椅的机会
And get out of that damn chair.
非常有诱惑力
Pretty tempting.
我能想象
I can imagine.
不  你不能
No, you can't.
说得对
You got me.
我从没失去过行动能力
I never been paralyzed.
但是我跟你说  我下过地狱
But I tell you something... I've been to hell,
那边还有个大天使等着拿我下油锅
And there's an archangel there wanting me to drop the soap.
你看看我  我比你倒霉多了
Look at me! My junk's rustier than yours!
你听见我腹痛了吗
You hear me bellyaching? Huh?
事实上  听见了
A-actually, yeah.
我心脏病犯了
I'm having a heart attack.
才不是
No, you're not.
那是什么
What is...
胃酸倒流
Acid reflux.
你这年岁有些东西不好消化
Guys your age can't digest certain foods.
不能吃奶酪汉堡了
You're gonna need to put down that cheeseburger.
你要继续发表感想
So, you want to keep emoting
还是谈谈怎么解决
Or you want to talk about solving
现在这个小问题
This little issue here.
毛病肯定在筹码上
It's got to be about the chips.
我把筹码推过去
I slid 'em across,
帕特里克施了巫术
Patrick did his little witchy number,
你立刻就年轻了
And you prettied up in a hurry.
我说  你们怎么想的
I mean, what are you all thinking?
是魔法筹码之类的东西
Some kind of magic chips or something?
绝对是
Definitely.
-咒语还记得吗  - 记得  一清二楚
- You remember what he chanted? - Yep... every word.
那好  我们就去查查他吧筹码藏在哪儿
All right, then let's find out where he stashes his chips.
给我偷50块出来
And steal me 50.
本杰明·巴顿《本杰明·巴顿奇事》又有汉堡吃了
Benjamin button me back into burger shape.
你说呢
What do you think?
我说你应该穿件衣服
I think you ought to put some clothes...
可以打扫房间吗
Ready for housekeeping, sir?
任何时候都可以
Born ready.
你跟我祖父一样
You're just like my grandfather.
他也是会动的东西都喜欢
He hits on anything that moves, too.
你真可爱
You're adorable.
而且危险
And dangerous.
我们走吧
Can we just go.
来人哪  他突然跑出来的
Guys, get some help! He came out of nowhere!
搞什么鬼
What the hell?
我得说
I got to say,
我有点儿喜欢这家伙
I kind of like the guy.
我就不上去了
Well, I'm out.
迪恩
Dean...
萨姆
Sam?
廉价商店型号
Dime-store model.
小事一桩
Piece of cake.
你真杯具  当心
Pathetic Watch out.
我能打开的
I could have done that.
你们在做什么
What are you doing?
你不是酒吧里那个妞么
Aren't you the chick from the bar?
我可不止如此
I'm a lot more than that.
没事了  宝贝儿
It's all right, sweetheart.
没事了  他们没有恶意
It's all right. They're harmless.
你们想要筹码  拿去吧
You boys want chips? Take 'em.
那些只是筹码  爱因斯坦们
They're just chips, Einsteins.
演出道具
It's showmanship.
你们可能会很吃惊
This may come as a shock,
但魔法并不存在于那些烂筹码上
But the magic does not lie in a pile of crappy plywood
也不是那些无用的咒语
Or in any phony abracadabra.
靠的是900岁的巫师
It's in the 900-year-old witch.
你们两想要恢复青春吗
You boys want years?
那就还是得按老规矩来
Score 'em the old-fashioned way.
德州扑克
Texas hold 'em.
好啊  放马过来吧
Fine. let's do it.
我手上这种牌是什么
What card am i holding up?
正如我所料
That's what i thought.
视力都已经退化了  那你的记忆力也不咋地了
If your eyesight's that bad, what about your memory?
我可不是侩子手
I'm not a murderer.
不过呢  你就不一样了
You, on the other hand...
-不行  萨姆  - 迪恩
- No, Sam. - Dean...
怎么  萨姆不太玩牌吗
What, Sam not much of a player?
好吧  那就一路顺风  迪恩
Okay, well, happy trails, Dean.
好好享受你的暮色人生吧
Enjoy the twilight of your life.
虽然你有机会搬回几成的
Should have taken better care of that ticker, though.
慢走不送了
You're free to go.
不过话又说回来  萨姆
Oh, but, Sam...
以你老哥的情况而言
Your brother's situation --
我可以就这么就算了
That's punishment enough,
我可不能让你这么简单地
But I can't let you leave
一点儿代价都不付出就拍拍屁股走人
Without a small parting gift.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
很快就会知道了
You'll find out soon enough.
我们闪  萨姆
Let's get out of here, Sam.
哥们
Dude...
我觉得那拍手绝对对你下咒了
I believe that he-witch gave you the clap.
帮忙推一把啊
Little help here?
我还是觉得我该跟他赌一次的
You know, I still think I should play.
不  不  想都别想
No, no, no.
你根本不够格
You're not good enough.
我算得上个中好手  鲍比更是个中高手
I'm better. Bobby's way better.
结果呢  我们都惨败了
We both lost.
没错
Exactly.
怎么  我连发言权都没有吗
So, what? so I don't get a say in this anymore?
萨姆  等你到了我们这个年纪
Sammy, when you get to be our age --
你才三十啊  迪恩
You're 30, Dean!
我就是看你赌牌这么久看都看会了
Look, I've watched you hustle plenty of poker --
会还远远不够  萨姆
Knowing the game is not enough, Sam.
这可不单单就是玩牌
It's not about playing the cards.
是跟对方玩心理  我也知道
It's about playing the other guy. I know that.
连这都懂了  真了不起
Well, hooray for you.
我要说的是  我跟那家伙交过手
All I'm saying is, I played this guy.
我知道他的手法  我对付得了他
I know his style. I can take him.
不  鲍比  你的时日也不太多了
No, Bobby. you don't have enough years in the bank.
足够了
I got enough.
不  一旦输了你就没命了  鲍比
No, you'll die if you lose, Bobby.
那我还能怎样呢
So what if i do, huh?
我活着是为了什么啊
What exactly am I living for, huh?!
等那该死的天启降世吗
The damn apocalypse?!
就因为我废在这轮椅上就该眼睁睁地看着大家死于非命
Watching men die bloody while I sit in this chair,
而无能为力吗
Can't take a step to help 'em?
鲍比
Bobby...
别  别阻止我  这是事实
No, no. it's the facts.
我年老
I'm old...
又体残
And broke down...
所以我不能再
And I can't...
我已经不再是猎魔人了
I ain't a hunter no more.
一无是处了
I'm useless.
要不是因为没勇气
And if I wasn't such a coward,
我早就该在从医院回来那天
I'd have stuck a gun in my mouth
就吞枪自刎一了百了了
Day I got home from the hospital.
鲍比  你不可以再去赌一次了
Bobby, you are not playing again.
我也不会  让你这么做的
I'm not... letting you do that.
肯定另有它法可解  肯定有的
There's another way out of this. there's got to be.
我一定会找到的
And I'm gonna find it.
拿着
Take it.
可以帮到你们
It'll help you.
什么东西
What is this?
你们闻所未闻的
The most powerful reversal spell
最强大的逆转法术
you've ever eye on
是逆转什么的
And it reverses what?
帕特里克的巫术  所有的
Patrick's work -- all of it.
你  你的意思是我能恢复正常
You -- you saying I could be normal again?
不止你  所有和他交过手的人都能恢复
You and everyone else he's ever played.
当然是还活着的
Who's still alive.
我们凭啥相信你呢
Why the hell should we trust you?
信不信随便  无所谓
Trust me, don't trust me. I don't care.
总而言之这法术是真的
The spell is real.
如果对所有人都有效  那岂不是也包括你的男人
If it zaps everyone, don't that include your man?
也包括对我
And me, too.
我本来就这样
I look good for my age.
女士  这加上去的可不少啊
Lady, this don't add up for squat.
你为什么要这么做
Why would you want that?
我自有原因
I have my reasons.
要做动作就要快
Do it quick.
我们明天就会离镇
We leave town tomorrow.
下注
Bet.
我觉得你这一局能扳回一城  海希
I sense you've got me by the jewels on this one, Hesh.
不跟
I fold.
你赢回多少年啊  貌似有13年吧  海希
What are you up -- like 13 years there, Hesh?
我看今天就到此为止吧  如何
What do you say we call it a day?
谢了  帕特里克
Thanks, Patrick.
海希来这儿是为了可以活着
Hesh here is gonna live
亲眼看到自己的孙女受洗礼
To see his granddaughter's bat mitzvah.
对吗  海希
Isn't that right, Hesh?
再次谢谢你  帕特里克
Thanks again, Patrick.
[希伯来语] 再见了  我的朋友  再见
Shalom, my friend. Shalom.
你还挺有良心的
That was nice of you.
我本来就是个有良心的人
I'm a nice guy.
有什么可以为你效劳的
What can I do you for?
发牌
Deal.
杀人犯的下颚骨  搞定了
Jawbone of a murderer. great.
知道吗  这主意真是糟透了
You know, this really sucks.
我们怎么确定她的法术会奏效呢
How do we even know her spell's gonna work?
没法确定  但我们有第二条路选吗
We don't. but we ain't got a plan "b."
所以别再唧唧歪歪了  继续挖吧
Now, less flappin' and more diggin'.
噢  偶滴神啊
Oh, god!
我的手肘  感觉全身都嘎吱嘎吱响了
My elbows! i'm all creaky.
速度些  别跟个小孩一样
Hurry up, you crybaby.
去你的  你倒是试试
Pound it up your ass, ironsides.
就一个小墓穴
One little grave.
那你来啊
Then you do it.
好  我马上飞过来
Fine. i'll hop right in.
至少你的腿没有知觉
Well, at least your legs are numb.
老爷爷  闭嘴吧
Shut up and dig, grandma.
我的背
Now it's my back!
你能站直吗
Can you straighten up?
能  但你表示下同情会死呀
Yeah, but a little sympathy wouldn't hurt.
屁股蛋有刺痛感吗
Butt cheek tingling?
这挺隐私的吧
Well, that's kind of personal.
那就是有咯
So "yeah"?
是坐骨神经痛  放心死不了  继续挖
It's sciatica. you'll live. keep digging.
听着  鲍比
You know, bobby...
干掉你  正式进入我的遗愿清单
Killing you is officially on my bucket list.
我喜欢你  萨姆  真的
I like you, sam. i do.
你很聪明  而且心地好
You're smart, and your heart's clearly in the right place.
单单是一眼  我就能看出一个人很多事
I can tell a lot about a guy by looking.
你是一个巫师么
You mean you're psychic.
不  那样是作弊
No. that'd be cheating.
我可是指传统的直觉哦
I'm talking about good old-fashioned intuition.
继续玩吧
Right. let's just play.
我们是在玩呀
We are playing.
你哥哥知道你在这里吗
Does your big brother know you're here?
5注
Bet five.
看样子不知道
Didn't think so.
加筹
I raise.
你在这里
Here you are, right...
试图去给他们擦屁股
Trying to clean up their mess,
但是他们还是想把你当小孩对待
And they still want to sit you at the kiddie table.
你不再是小弟弟了  萨姆
You're not the little brother anymore, sam.
不过呢
Then again...
你也许是
...maybe you are.
你有点理解不了了吧
You're in over your head here, sam.
你当然可以继续这么做
I mean, you can keep making these moves --
好比说
You know...
小心翼翼的下注
Playing it cautious,
计算几率
Playing the percentages.
不过我还是会把你送进敬老院的
But i'm still gonna kick your arse into the nursing home.
是不是这种空谈心理学
Does this armchair-psychology routine
对你来说常常有效吗
Usually work for you?
你说呢
You tell me.
你是那个正在输的
You're the one who's losing.
休息一下好么
Little break?
那边怎么样了
How's it going in there?
你以为会怎么样
How do you think it's going?
你那边呢  找到你要找的东西没
What about you? you have everything you need?
我们还是要找到那男巫的DNA
We still need a little he-witch dna.
他之前叼着这个
He was chewing it.
赶紧  迪恩
Hurry up, dean. please.
好  别让他空下来
All right. just keep him busy.
还有萨姆
And, sammy...
别输了
Don't lose.
扔进去
Drop it in.
怎样
Well?
我看起来怎样
How do i look?
提问
Question --
你是想把这个给你哥哥吗
Is this what you meant to give your big brother?
你给他的那根我从来没碰过嘴唇
The one you gave him never passed my lips.
屁用都没有
Won't do a scrap of good.
我可不喜欢作弊  萨姆
I don't like cheating, sam.
停下来  帕特里克  放了他
Stop it! patrick, let him go!
他想要杀了我们
He tried to kill us!
是我做的  我给他的咒语
I did it! i gave him the spell!
什么
What?
为什么
Why...
你为什么那么做
Why would you do that?
你知道为什么
You know why.
你知道
You know.
继续玩
Keep...playing.
每样东西我们都没弄错啊
Everything we put in that spell was kosher.
对啊  就是除了那个该死的牙签
Yeah, everything except the damn toothpick.
你必须拿到些DNA
You got to go get a speck of dna.
得抓紧了
Strap on your track shoes.
太好了
Oh, goody.
又得走楼梯
More stairs.
这里真他娘的干净
It's too damn clean in here.
我算是第一次碰见
First witch i ever heard of
不乱吐唾沫的巫师
Didn't spew bodily fluids all over the place.
牙刷  梳子  随便什么东西
Toothbrush, comb -- anything.
看看你
Well, look at you --
计算型玩家要全压了啊
The percentage player betting the farm.
这可不行哦  萨姆
Awful transparent of you, sam.
要是我手气像你那么好
I mean, if i had a monster hand like you have,
我就会算计你
I'd trap you.
但是你过于兴奋了
But you get so excited,
把鸡蛋都放到一个篮子里
You bet yourself right out of a big pot.
合牌
I fold.
我猜是一对Q
Set of ladies, i'm guessing.
偷鸡偷的不错么
Nice bluff.
要是我们有时间  我真会跟你好好玩玩
If we had time, i could make a real player out of you.
我有时间
I got time.
也许
Maybe.
但是迪恩可以不一定了
But i can't say the same for dean.
你哥哥马上就要死了
Your brother's gonna be dead soon.
我说的马上
And when i say "soon"...
是指分钟哟
I mean minutes.
我说结束之前  游戏不会结束
The game's not over till i say it is.
盲注
Blinds.
事关你兄弟的时候
So, when it's about your brother,
你就变得情绪激动
You get so emotional,
你的心思完全就飞了出去
Your brain just flies right out the window.
很好
Good to know.
见鬼去吧
Go to hell.
我全押
I'm all-in.
别这样  萨姆
Don't do that, sam.
只有结束了我才能走
I can't leave until it's over?
那就让它结束
Fine. it's over.
说  我哥哥在哪儿
Now, where's my brother?
听着  你这样玩牌  无异于自杀
Look, there's poker and then there's suicide.
快点来吧
Just play the hand.
迪恩  你怎么了
Dean? dean, you there?
好吧
Fine.
迪恩
Dean?!
我很抱歉  小子
I'm sorry, kid.
三条A
Aces full.
你在哭
You're crying.
作为一个女巫你很善良  但这样却有点毛骨悚然
For a witch, you're so nice, it's actually kind of creepy.
没事
It's okay.
确实是好牌
It was a great hand.
只是
Just...
这还是
...not as great...
比不上4条4
...as four 4s.
玩得不错啊
Well played.
要知道  刚才那一套
You know, that whole...
使你失去理智的言论
Going-out-of-your-head bit --
真的非常奏效
Very method.
看来你真的很不简单
Well, there's more to you than meets the eye.
这些筹码全部给迪恩
Cash these in for dean, please.
乐意效劳
With pleasure.
迪恩  你听到了吗
Dean, you hear me?
见鬼  迪恩
Damn it, dean!
真是呆子
Idjit.
我做不到
I can't do this.
你可以的
Yes, you can.
别逼我
Don't make me.
我不想赢
I don't want to win.
我埋葬了自己的女儿
I buried my daughter.
她变成了这样
And she looked like this.
这一切是不正常的
It's not natural.
你知道的
You knew...
自从你选择和我在一起
When you decided to come with me.
你也就选择了这一切
This is what you wanted.
你依然年轻
You're still young.
如此美丽
You're so beautiful.
你有我
You have me.
我想念我的家人
I miss my family.
我很抱歉  帕特里克
I'm sorry, patrick.
我以为你爱我
I thought you loved me.
我爱你
I do.
亲爱的  我当然爱你
Sweetheart, of course I do.
我以为我能断绝过去
I thought I was cut out for this,
但我错了
But I'm not.
我不能没有你
I don't think i can do this without you.
在你遇见我之前  很久以来  你也过得很好
You got on okay for a long time before you met me.
下注吧
Check.
全押
All-in.
谢谢你
Thank you.
没有出千  你凭实力打败了那家伙吗
No tricks -- you actually beat the guy?
真的假的
How the hell?
走运而已
Just lucky.
回头见  伙计们
Hey. I'll see y'all guys later.
去哪儿
Where you going?
没什么
Mm, nowhere.
去打疫苗
A booster shot.
闭嘴
Don't say it.
我想我们该把东西装上车吧
Well, I guess we can get the van loaded.
我不该说你是笨蛋
I shouldn't have called you an idiot.
你是说哪次
Which time?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我是说  我真的
I mean, I actually -- I-I...
我理解了
I get it.
衰老可不是单身派对
Getting old ain't a bachelor party.
再加上你所在的处境
And dealing with the crap you got to deal with...
少来说什么同情的话
Don't you go on pity patrol.
不  我没有
I'm not.
我不是这个意思
I'm not. I'm just...
我是说  如果我是你
I'm saying, you know, if I was in your shoes...
你会喋喋不休抱怨到死
You'd never stop complaining.
好吧
Fair enough.
你不是毫无用处的  鲍比
You're not useless, bobby.
好吧
Okay.
说得不错
Good talk.
等等  你听我说
No, wait a minute. listen to me.
即使士兵在战斗中负伤
You don't stop being a soldier
也不会因此而退出
'cause you got wounded in battle.
明白吗  不管你变成什么样
Okay? No matter what shape you're in,
最起码  你是我们的家人
Bottom line is, you're family.
你可能没注意
I don't know if you've noticed,
但我和萨姆  已经没有多少可牵绊的人
But me and sam, we don't have much left.
我不能没有你
I can't do this without you.
我做不到
I can't.
决不允许你再说要退出
So don't you dare think about checking out.
我不想再听到第二遍
I don't want to hear that again.
好吧
Okay.
好吗
很好
Good.
多谢
Thanks.
我们肉麻完了吗
Now, we done feeling our feelings?
在我们开始越来越像娘们之前
'cause I'd like to get out of this room
我想离开这房间了
Before we both start growing lady parts.
说完了
Yeah, we're done.
走吧  轮椅神探
Let's go, ironsides.
非这样叫我吗
Oh, that one's sticking, huh?